http://www.beeskneeskids.com/pages/privacy-policy

Fairy Finery: Privacy Policy
Contact Us
Become a Wholesaler
Log in
Cart (0)
Privacy Policy
We recognize that you care how information about you is used and shared.
We have created this Privacy Policy to inform you of our information collection, use and sharing practices for this Web site. Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy apply only to information gathered through this Web site and, where applicable, through our Customer Service Department in connection with this Web site, and do not necessarily reflect our practices with respect to information gathered through other Web sites that we operate or through other off-line means. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you should contact our Customer Service Department by clicking on “Contact Us” within the toolbar area of this Web site.
What Information about me is collected and stored?
We collect and store information that you enter into this Web site or that you provide to our Customer Service Department. For example, when you open an account or place an order, we collect and store some or all of the following information that you provide: name, billing address, shipping address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number and expiration date (Please note credit card information is temporarily stored for authorization purposes only). This information is used to provide the products and services that you have ordered or requested, to process and ship orders, to send order and shipping confirmations and to provide customer service. This information also may be used to contact you about sales, special offers and new site features, unless you have opted not to receive promotional communications in connection with this Web site. We collect and store certain other information automatically whenever you interact with this Web site. For example, we collect your IP address, browser information every time you visit this Web site. We also collect information regarding customer traffic patterns and site usage. This information is used to analyze and improve this Web site and to provide our customers with a fulfilling shopping experience. Also, like many Web sites, we use “cookies”, which are files stored on your computer’s hard drive by your browser. Cookies help us to identify account holders and to optimize their shopping experience. Cookies also allow us to hold selections in a shopping cart when a user leaves this Web site without checking out. Most browsers accept cookies automatically but allow you to disable them. We recommend that you leave cookies “turned on” so that we can offer you a better shopping experience on this Web site.
Is Information Collected From Children?
We do not sell or ship any items ordered through this Web site directly to anyone who we know to be under the age of 18, nor do we collect any personal information from anyone who we know to be under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, you should use this Web site only with the involvement of a parent or guardian and should not submit any personal information to us.
With whom do you share Information?
We do not share or sell with others any personal information that you provide to us through this Web site or through our Customer Service Department, except with your consent or as described in this Privacy Policy. We engage third parties to perform services in connection with the operation of our business. Examples of these services include payment processing and authorization, fraud protection and credit risk reduction, product customization, order fulfillment and shipping, marketing and promotional material distribution, Web site evaluation, data analysis and, where applicable, data cleansing. We provide personal information to these third parties, but we authorize them to use this information only in connection with the services they perform. We may release personal information if we believe in good faith that: the law or legal process requires it; we have received a valid administrative request from a law enforcement agency; or such release is necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of this web site or any of our affiliates, business partners, customers or others. We may share non-personal information with our marketing partners, advertisers and others from time to time. Examples of such non-personal information include the number of users who visited this Web site during a specific time period or purchased a specific product through this Web site. This information generally is shared in an aggregated form. As with any business, it is possible that as our business develops, we might sell or buy online stores or other assets. In such transactions, information about customers often is among the transferred assets. Accordingly, in the unlikely event that all of our assets are acquired by a third party, such information may be one of the transferred assets (unless the information was collected under a previous Privacy Policy that did not permit such disclosure). Under such circumstances, we would to the extent possible require the acquiring party to follow the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
What Steps Are Taken To Keep Personal Information Secure?
We use various security measures, including Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology to ensure protection on your credit card information each and every time you place an order on this web site. Prior to placing an order through this Web site, you will be asked to set up an account and provide an e-mail address and password. You must provide an appropriate e-mail address and password in order to access account information. In order to help protect your personal information further, you should be careful about providing your password to others. If you wish to cancel a password, or if you become aware of any loss, theft or unauthorized use of a password, please contact us immediately by clicking on “Contact Us” within the toolbar area of this Web site, you can also change your password by clicking on “My Account” within the toolbar area of this Web site.
Can I Indicate Whether or Not I Want To Receive Promotional Communications?
There are several ways in which you can tell us whether or not you want to receive promotional communications from us. When you set up an account, or click on “My Account” within the Toolbar area, you will have an opportunity to make or change your selections in this regard. What Happens When I Link To or From Another Web Site? This Web site may contain links to Web sites operated by third parties. Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy do not apply to information gathered through these other Web sites. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave this Web site and to read the privacy policies of each and every Web site that you visit.
How Will I Be Informed About Changes Regarding This Privacy Policy?
If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on this Web site notifying users of the changes. In some cases, we also may send an e-mail notifying users of the changes. You should check this Web site periodically to see if any recent changes to this Privacy Policy have occurred.
Help
Customer & Product Care
Gift Certificates
Shipping & Returns
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use
Become a Wholesaler
© 2020 Fairy Finery.
Studio-made in the USA.
Powered by Shopify
Size Chart
